

tayrwelling@gmail.com 605-270-1773 taylorwelling.com github.com/tw3080 linkedin.com/in/taylorwelling

SUMMARY

Passionate about combining design and technical skills to build exceptional user experiences. Strives to produce content that is aesthetically pleasing and functional, and takes pride in using empathy to understand projects from the user's perspective. Possesses a strong drive for self-improvement and an openness to ideas and input from others; an excellent member of any team.

EXPERIENCE

Poké Mongo (October 2016)

- Allows Pokémon card collectors to quickly view and manage their cards online
- Users can sign up, login, and search for cards to add to their virtual collection
- Developed with HTML5, CSS3/LESS, JavaScript (ES6), AngularJS, Node.js, Express, and MongoDB

Weather Mood (August 2016)

- Weather app with changing styles and white noise sounds based on weather conditions
- Designed to be unobtrusive and relaxing; concisely displays only the most essential weather information
- Users can search for locations and save their favorite cities for quick viewing
- Developed with HTML5, CSS3/LESS, JavaScript, and AngularJS

Mappr (July 2016)

- An interactive gallery and map of Flickr photos which integrates the Flickr API and Google Maps API to display photos based on locations searched for by the user
- Developed with HTML5, CSS3/LESS, JavaScript, and jQuery

SKILLS

Development

HTML5 | CSS3 | LESS | JavaScript | AngularJS | jQuery | Node.js | Express | MongoDB

Design

Responsive Web Design | UI / UX Design | Wireframing

Software

Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator | Git/GitHub

EDUCATION

Thinkful (May 2016 – December 2016)

Remote

- Intensive full-stack JavaScript development course
- Project-based curriculum with 1-on-1 mentorship from senior engineers

Bellevue College (April 2015 – May 2016)

Bellevue, WA

- Completed 45 credits towards AAS in Computer Science
- Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society

San Jacinto College (August 2011 – May 2013)

Pasadena, TX

- Completed 48 credits towards AA in General Studies
- Dean's list fall '11, spring '12, fall '12

WORK HISTORY

Crew Member

Trader Joe's (October 2016 – Present)

Food Server

Scotty Browns (August 2014 – October 2015) Olive Garden (November 2013 – August 2014)